Search the docs

K

#### Account & Sales

#### Photo AI

#### Video AI

#### Gigapixel AI

#### Other Apps

Privacy Policy
==============

### What site information do we collect?​

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or email support.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information.

### Application data collection​

Installed Topaz software may collect and transmit usage data for the application. This data includes events such as the opening of the application, and the opening and processing of image files. It does not include the actual names of images or their content. This data is associated with an anonymized user id, and the collection of this data can be disabled in application preferences without any loss of product function.

In addition, some of our applications have a voluntary rating system function. This lets one click a button to submit feedback about the quality of the application output. When explicitly submitted by the user, a portion of the currently processed image may be included in this submission. This data is associated with an anonymized user id.

### What do we use your information for?​

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

1. To personalize your experience: Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs
2. To improve our website: We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you
3. To improve customer service: Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs
4. To process transactions: Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
5. To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
6. To send periodic emails: The email address you provide may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
7. To send periodic SMS after opt-in: Should you choose to opt-in, the phone number you provide may be used to send you informational text messages related to your orders, along with occasional updates about our company, and related product or service information.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, click the “Manage My Subscription” or “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of each newsletter or email.

### How do we protect your information?​

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway provider’s (Paypal) database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

### Do we use cookies?​

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?​

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third party links​

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance​

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

### Online Privacy Policy Only​

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### Terms and Conditions​

Please also visit our [Terms and Conditions](https://topazlabs.com/terms) section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy​

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on **May 14, 2024**.

### Contacting Us​

All requests for further information or for permission to reproduce any portions of the Materials should be directed to:

Topaz Labs LLC​

14555 Dallas Pkwy, Ste 350​

Dallas, Texas 75254​

On this page
------------
